Don T. Young Photographic Negatives MS088
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Don T. Young Photographic Negatives
1963 -- 1981
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Young, Don T.
MS088
3 Linear Feet 6 boxes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains negatives (35 mm and 4x5) of people and events at Tufts from 1965 to 1981. The majority of the subject matter is athletics.
Biographical / Historical
Don T. Young was a freelance photographer who photographed many people and events at Tufts between 1965 and 1981.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; University history; Young, Don T.
- Don T. Young negatives, college events, 1963 -- 1981; 1965 -- 1981; MS088.001; 1.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains negatives (35 mm and 4x5) of people and events at Tufts from 1965 to 1981. The majority of the subject matter is athletics.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Negatives, 1965; MS088.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1965; MS088.001.001.00001.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: April 1965, Lacrosse. Slot 5-7: April 1965, Baseball.
    - Negatives, 1965; MS088.001.001.00001.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: April 1965, Baseball.
  - Negatives, 1966; MS088.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1966; MS088.001.001.00002.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: June 1, 1966, Annual Northeastern States Youth Citizenship Conference
    - Negatives, 1966; MS088.001.001.00002.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: June 1, 1966, Annual Northeastern States Youth Citizenship Conference. Slot 4-7: April 9, 1966, Kids Day at Tufts
    - Negatives, 1966; MS088.001.001.00002.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: April 9, 1966, Kids Day at Tufts. Slot 4-7: Baseball
    - Negatives, 1966; MS088.001.001.00002.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Candids of Rocco Carzo and other grid coaches
    - Negatives, 1966; MS088.001.001.00002.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: Candids of Rocco Carzo and other grid coaches Slot 5-7: Soccer action, cross-country runners Paul Thompson and Paul Carlin, sailing -- Dave Curtin and Ding Dussault.
    - Negatives, 1966; MS088.001.001.00002.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Soccer action, cross-country runners Paul Thompson and Paul Carlin, sailing -- Dave Curtin and Ding Dussault.
  - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Tufts University, April 21, 1967, at Cohen Arts Center
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Unidentified. Slot 7: Tufts University, May 16, 1967, Capt. Nufer Air Force ROTC Class
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Tufts University, May 16, 1967, Capt. Nufer Air Force ROTC Class. Slot 3-4: Tufts University, April 21, 1967, Shakespearian Class, Outdoors. Slot 5: 1967 Tufts. Slot 6-7: Tufts University, April 11, 1967, Voice of America.
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: Tufts University, April 11, 1967, Voice of America. Slot 5-7: Tufts University, May 1, 1967, Junior Day
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: Tufts University, May 1, 1967, Junior Day. Slot 2: Tufts University, May 16, 1967, Dr. Sussman & Student in Chemical Engineering Experiment. Slot 5: 1967 Tufts. Slot 6-7: 1967 Assembly
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Candid picture of Rocky Corzo at Tufts. Slot 3-5: Cousins Gym for Bill Wells, 6/7/1967. Slot 6-7: Rocky Carzo & Sailing Cup, 6/7/1967.
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00007 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: 9/16/1967, Football vs. AIC (scrimmage). Slot 3-7: 3/30/1967, baseball and lacrosse singles.
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00008 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: 3/30/1967 baseball and lacrosse singles.
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00009 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Football scrimmage vs. Utica, 9/16/1967.
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00010 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Football action singles, 9/2/1967.
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00011 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1967; MS088.001.001.00003.00012 (Box 1)
  - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: Tufts University, May 29, 1968, Bicycle Engineering Project. Slot 5-7: April 27, 1968, "Kids Day at Tufts."
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: April 27, 1968, "Kids Day at Tufts." Slot 6-7: Tufts University, November 27, 1968, c/o Prof. J.J. McKeown, National Council for Air and Stream Improvement, Inc.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Tufts University, November 27, 1968, c/o Prof. J.J. McKeown, National Council for Air and Stream Improvement, Inc.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Tufts University, Feb. 19, 1968, Library Windows. Slot 7: Jan 25, 1968, Engineering picture of Cox and Norton's airplane project.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Jan 25, 1968, Engineering picture of Cox and Norton's airplane project.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Jan 25, 1968, Engineering picture of Cox and Norton's airplane project. Slot 3-7: Tufts University, June 5-6, 1968, Northeastern States Youth Citizenship Conference at B.C.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00007 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Tufts University, June 5-6, 1968, Northeastern States Youth Citizenship Conference at B.C.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00008 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00009 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: March 22, 1968, Pops Night at Tufts
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00010 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00011 (Box 1)
      Slot: 1-7: March 22, 1968, Pops Night at Tufts
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00012 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Tufts University, June 25, 1968, Prof. Hill, Tufts Dental School. Slot 7: April 11, 1968, Sen. McCarthy at Lincoln-Filene Center.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00013 (Box 1)
      Slot: 1-7: April 11, 1968, Sen. McCarthy at Lincoln-Filene Center.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00014 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Tufts University, April 11, 1968, Baseball and soccer singles.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00015 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: Tufts University, April 11, 1968, Baseball and soccer singles. Slot 4-7: April 2, 1968, Tufts Assembly
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00016 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: April 2, 1968, Tufts Assembly.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00017 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: April 2, 1968, Tufts Assembly.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00018 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Basketball, swimming, wrestling singles, 12/6/1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00019 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: Basketball, swimming, wrestling singles, 12/6/1968. Slot 6-7: Day Camp, 7/8/1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00020 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Day Camp, 7/8/1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00021 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00022 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: Day Camp, 7/8/1968. Slot 5-7: Football player Rich Giachetti, 12/6/1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00004.00023 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: Football player Rich Giachetti, 12/6/1968. Slot 2-7: Portraits of Rocky Carzo and Harry Arlerson, 6/19/1968.
  - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: Portraits of Rocky Carzo and Harry Arlerson, 6/19/1968. Slot 5-7: Track action, Golf singles, 5/8/1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Track action, Golf singles, 5/8/1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: Track action, Golf singles, 5/8/1968. Slot 2-7: football and soccer action, 9/21/1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: football and soccer action, 9/21/1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: football and soccer action, 9/21/1968. Slot 3-7: football candid action, August 1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: football candid action, August 1968.
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00007 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00008 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00009 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00010 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1968; MS088.001.001.00005.00011 (Box 1)
  - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Oct. 25, 1969, Tufts Alumni Seminar - Homecoming Day. Slot 7: Tufts University, Oct. 15, 1969, Moratorium Day.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Tufts University, Oct. 15, 1969, Moratorium Day.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Tufts University, Oct. 15, 1969, Moratorium Day. Slot 3-7: Tufts University, Nov. 6, 1969, Student Takeover of Construction Site.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Nov. 10, 1969, Demonstrators at New Building Under Construction.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Sept. 28, 1969, Tufts University, Arlo Guthrie Concert.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Sept. 28, 1969, Tufts University, Arlo Guthrie Concert. Slot 7: Tufts University, May 31, 1969, Alumni Day.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00007 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: Tufts University, May 31, 1969, Alumni Day. Slot 6-7: May 31 & June 1, 1969, Alumni Day and wedding.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00008 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: May 31 & June 1, 1969, Alumni Day and wedding. Slot 3-5: Tufts University, March 13, 1969, Baseball Team at Logan Airport leaves for Mexico City, Mexico. Slot 6-7: Tufts University, Sept. 4, 1969, Freshman Orientation Seminars and head/shoulders of P.R. staff.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00009 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Tufts University, Sept. 4, 1969, Freshman Orientation Seminars and head/shoulders of P.R. staff.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00010 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: Tufts University, Sept. 4, 1969, Freshman Orientation Seminars and head/shoulders of P.R. staff. Slot 4-5: Nov. 6, 1969, Students Meet in Cohen Auditorium. Slot 6-7: Tufts University, Nov. 25, 1969, Play rehearsal of "Amhal & Niglot visitors."
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00011 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: Tufts University, Dec. 14, 1969, Beelzebubs - Candids of each member. Slot 6-7: Tufts University, Dec. 18, 1969, Donald Robertson at dissection.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00012 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: Tufts University, Dec. 18, 1969, Donald Robertson at dissection. Slot 2-7: Aug. 5-6-7, 1967, Alumni Summer Study Program.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00013 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Aug. 5-6-7, 1967, Alumni Summer Study Program. Slot 7: June 4, 1969, Portraits of Harry Andanson and Daniel (last name illegible).
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00014 (Box 1)
      Slot: 1-4: June 4, 1969, Portraits of Harry Andanson and Daniel (last name illegible). Slot 5-7: June 1, 1969, Commencement.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00015 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: June 1, 1969, Commencement.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00016 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: June 1, 1969, Commencement. Slot 3-7: Jan. 18, 1969, Alumni Leaders Symposium.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00017 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Jan. 18, 1969, Alumni Leaders Symposium.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00018 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: Jan. 18, 1969, Alumni Leaders Symposium. Slot 4-7: Sept. 3, 1969, Football Singles (action).
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00019 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Sept. 3, 1969, Football Singles (action).
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00020 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00021 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00022 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00006.00023 (Box 1)
  - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00007.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: Baseball pics of Bob Kart, 1/20/1969. Slot 4-7: Track Meet vs. N.H., 2/19/1969.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00007.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Track Meet vs. N.H., 2/19/1969.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00007.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Track Meet vs. N.H., 2/19/1969. Slot 3-7: baseball & lacrosse action, 4/28/1969.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00007.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: baseball & lacrosse action, 4/28/1969. Slot 2-3: All-sports banquet, 5/1/1969. Slot 4-7: Basketball vs. Harvard, 1/13/1964.
    - Negatives, 1969; MS088.001.001.00007.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: Basketball vs. Harvard, 1/13/1964. Slot 4-6: Soccer singles - 2 players, 11/4/1969.
  - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: December 12, 1970, Trustees Meeting.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: December 12, 1970, Trustees Meeting. Slot 3-7: June 10, 1970, Lee J. Cobb, actor.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: June 10, 1970, Lee J. Cobb, actor. Slot 7: April 25, 1970, Tufts University Jumbo Club Awards Dinner.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: April 25, 1970, Tufts University Jumbo Club Awards Dinner. Slot 2-4: April 7, 1970, Mrs. Martin Luther King, Jr. Slot 5-7: March 5, 1970, Seminar demonstration of machine.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: March 5, 1970, Seminar demonstration of machine. Slot 2: March 3, 1970, Bob Bass and professor with certificate. Slot 3-7: January 14, 1970, Doble Doll Collection / physics professors with students.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: January 15, 1970, Environmental Studies Faculty Committee. Slot 4-7: September 9, 1970, Freshman Orientation Day.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00007 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: September 9, 1970, Freshman Orientation Day.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00008 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Baseball, lacrosse, tennis, track teams and singles, 4/25/70.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00009 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00010 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Graduation, 5/31/70.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00011 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Graduation, 5/31/70. Slot 7: Award to Rich Giachetto, 5/18/1970.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00012 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Award to Rich Giachetto, 5/18/1970. Slot 3: sailing and track teams, 4/30/1970. Slot 4-7: "Ding" Dussault Cage Dedication, 2/25/1970.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00013 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: "Ding" Dussault Cage Dedication, 2/25/1970. Slot 2-7: basketball, track, swimming, and wrestling -- singles, 2/12/1970.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00014 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: basketball, track, swimming, and wrestling -- singles, 2/12/1970. Slot 6-7: wrestling championships, 11/24/1970.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00015 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: wrestling championships, 11/24/1970. Slot 4-7: gym, cage, pod, practice field, 11/9/1970.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00016 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: gym, cage, pod, practice field, 11/9/1970. Slot 3-6: Football vs. N.Y., 11/14/1970. Slot 7: basketball singles, 11/17/1970.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00017 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: basketball singles, 11/17/1970. Slot 3-5: Newly elected football captains for 1971 season, 11/25/1970. Slot 6-7: Grid portraits - football, 9/1/1970.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00018 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Grid portraits - football, 9/1/1970.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00019 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00020 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Grid Action Individuals - football, 9/1/1970.
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00021 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00022 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1970; MS088.001.001.00008.00023 (Box 1)
  - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: March 27, 1971, President's Ball.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: March 27, 1971, President's Ball. Slot 4-7: December 9, 1971, Department of Civil Engineering, James J. McKeown.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: December 9, 1971, Department of Civil Engineering, James J. McKeown.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: December 9, 1971, Department of Civil Engineering, James J. McKeown. Slot 4-7: November 30, 1971, Former Prime Minister Harold Wilson.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: November 30, 1971, Former Prime Minister Harold Wilson. Slot 3-7: January-February 1971, Recruitment.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: January-February 1971, Recruitment.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00007 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00008 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00009 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00010 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: January-February 1971, Recruitment. Slot 2-7: June 6, 1971, Tufts graduation.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00011 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: June 6, 1971, Tufts graduation.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00012 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: June 6, 1971, Tufts graduation. Slot 4-7: April 8, 1971, Admissions personnel.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00013 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: April 8, 1971, Admissions personnel.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00014 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: April 8, 1971, Admissions personnel.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00015 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Group for Bob Poulson, 7/13/1971. Slot 3-4: Award to John Dember from Sport Magazine, 1/26/1971. Slot 5-7: Track Meet with Holy Cross, 1/20/71.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00016 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: New Machine for Paul Rich, 7/13/1971. Slot 4-7: Football Candids, 7/1/1971.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00017 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Football Candids, 7/1/1971.
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00018 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00019 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00020 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00021 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1971; MS088.001.001.00009.00022 (Box 1)
  - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: February 8, 1972, Engineering students and toys for child with cerebral palsy.
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Baseball singles, 4/6/1972.
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: Baseball singles, 4/6/1972. Slot 2-5: football and golf captains, May 1972. Slot 6-7: football singles, 9/15/72.
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: football singles, 9/15/72.
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: football singles, 9/15/72. Slot 7: soccer team singles, 9/22/1972.
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: soccer team singles, 9/22/1972.
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00007 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Mohammed Ali addressing students, 10/9/1972. Slot 7: Dance Marathon, 10/28/1972.
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00008 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Dance Marathon, 10/28/1972. Slot 3-7: Sailing, cross country teams, other features 11/16/1972.
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00009 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Sailing, cross country teams, other features 11/16/1972. Slot 3-5: Conference of International Business Leaders at Fletcher, 12/2/72. Slot 6-7: presentation of university steering committee report to President Hallowell, 12/22/1972.
    - Negatives, 1972; MS088.001.001.00010.00010 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: presentation of university steering committee report to President Hallowell, 12/22/1972.
  - Negatives, 1973; MS088.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1973; MS088.001.001.00011.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: Pop Houston Award, 9/26/1973. Slot 4-7: basketball action vs. Springfield and Suffolk and Singles, 1/11/73.
    - Negatives, 1973; MS088.001.001.00011.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: basketball action vs. Springfield and Suffolk and Singles, 1/11/73.
    - Negatives, 1973; MS088.001.001.00011.00003 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1973; MS088.001.001.00011.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: basketball action vs. Springfield and Suffolk and Singles, 1/11/73. Slot 7: basketball team, 1/11/1973.
  - Negatives, 1974; MS088.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1974; MS088.001.001.00012.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Football groups, singles, 9/8/1974.
    - Negatives, 1974; MS088.001.001.00012.00002 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1974; MS088.001.001.00012.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: Football groups, singles, 9/8/1974. Slot 2-5: NCASI Anderson Hall c/o Jim McKeoan, 12/31/1974.
  - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: May 2, 1975, Harvard University protest at Massachusetts Hall.
    - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: May 2, 1975, Harvard University protest at Massachusetts Hall. Slot 4-7: December 29, 1975, Tufts University, National Council for Air and Stream Improvement, Inc.
    - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: December 29, 1975, Tufts University, National Council for Air and Stream Improvement, Inc.
    - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Tim Whelan, 11/10/1975. Slot 7: basketball star Dennis Mink, 2/15/1975.
    - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: basketball star Dennis Mink, 2/15/1975. Slot 6-7: Football -- singles, groups, 9/14/1975.
    - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Football -- singles, groups, 9/14/1975.
    - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013.00007 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: Football -- singles, groups, 9/14/1975. Slot 5-7: Football vs. Colby.
    - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013.00008 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Football vs. Colby.
    - Negatives, 1975; MS088.001.001.00013.00009 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: Football vs. Colby.
  - Negatives, 1976; MS088.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1976; MS088.001.001.00014.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: December 20, 1976, Tufts University, National Council for Air and Stream Improvement, Inc. Slot 5: May 20, 1976, Reception for M. Campbell. Slot 6-7: May 5, 1976, Luncheon for Boston Morning Country Club.
    - Negatives, 1976; MS088.001.001.00014.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: May 5, 1976, Luncheon for Boston Morning Musicales at Brookline Country Club. Slot 2-3: May 2, 1976, Alumni inducted into honor society.
    - Negatives, 1976; MS088.001.001.00014.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-2: Tufts women's basketball, 1/20/1976. Slot 3-5: N.E. Football Writers Awards / Harry Agganis ward to Tim Whelan, 11/29/1976. Slot 6-7: Bulgei Lowe Award to Tim Whelan, 12/15/1976.
  - Negatives, 1978; MS088.001.001.00015 (Box 1)